{
    "subject": "resource/The_Romance_of_Old_Bill",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:1918_films",
    "human_readable": "The Romance of Old Bill is about 1918 films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7247486114501953,
            "question": "What year were the films described in 'The Romance of Old Bill' made?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.721101701259613,
            "question": "Is 'The Romance of Old Bill' a book or a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6634654998779297,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the type of films depicted in 'The Romance of Old Bill'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4429643750190735,
            "question": "Are there any similar films from around 1918 that you know of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43555426597595215,
            "question": "What is the lasting impact of these types of films from 1918?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4131247401237488,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors associated with 'The Romance of Old Bill'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3504534959793091,
            "question": "What is the main theme explored in 'The Romance of Old Bill'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30104488134384155,
            "question": "How did audiences likely react to 'The Romance of Old Bill' upon its release?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08214821666479111,
            "question": "Where were these films likely distributed or shown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06897328048944473,
            "question": "What historical context might have influenced the creation of these films?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Romance of Old Bill is about 1918 films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1188_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where were these films likely distributed or shown?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1188_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did audiences likely react to 'The Romance of Old Bill' upon its release?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1188_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the main theme explored in 'The Romance of Old Bill'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1188_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1188_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1188_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1188_137.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1188_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1188_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1188_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1188_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1188_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1188_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1188_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provided contain information related to the film \"The Better \u00e2\u0080\u0099ole; or, The Romance of Old Bill,\" which was indeed filmed in 1918. This supports the statement that \"The Romance of Old Bill\" is about 1918 films."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}